<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<response>
<lst name="responseHeader"><int name="status">0</int><int name="QTime">1</int><lst name="params"><str name="q">user_id:254</str></lst></lst><result name="response" numFound="1" start="0"><doc><str name="user_last_name">Munden</str><str name="user_id">254</str><date name="doc_upload_date">2013-10-15T00:00:00Z</date><str name="linkedin_positions">{"_total":8,"values":[{"company":{"industry":"Design","name":"Freelance"},"id":441714457,"isCurrent":true,"startDate":{"month":8,"year":2013},"title":"Graphic Designer &amp; Artworker"},{"company":{"id":407310,"industry":"Medical Devices","name":"Olympus KeyMed","size":"1001-5000 employees","type":"Privately Held"},"endDate":{"month":8,"year":2013},"id":180936339,"isCurrent":false,"startDate":{"month":4,"year":2000},"title":"Senior Graphic Designer"},{"company":{"industry":"Design","name":"Thames Card Technology"},"endDate":{"month":4,"year":2000},"id":441715619,"isCurrent":false,"startDate":{"month":4,"year":1998},"title":"Design Studio Manager"},{"company":{"industry":"Design","name":"Fairway Litho Print"},"endDate":{"month":4,"year":1998},"id":441715906,"isCurrent":false,"startDate":{"month":11,"year":1995},"title":"Designer, Typesetter and Scitex System Operator"},{"company":{"industry":"Design","name":"Cloverleaf Graphics"},"endDate":{"month":11,"year":1995},"id":441716075,"isCurrent":false,"startDate":{"month":6,"year":1991},"title":"Designer, Typesetter and Crosfield System Operator"},{"company":{"industry":"Design","name":"Kall-Kwik Printing"},"endDate":{"month":6,"year":1991},"id":441716218,"isCurrent":false,"startDate":{"month":6,"year":1989},"title":"Head of Art Department"},{"company":{"industry":"Design","name":"Redlin Print Limited"},"endDate":{"month":3,"year":1989},"id":441716382,"isCurrent":false,"startDate":{"month":7,"year":1987},"title":"Graphic Designer"},{"company":{"industry":"Design","name":"Creative Services Ltd &amp; Pip Printers"},"endDate":{"month":7,"year":1987},"id":441718488,"isCurrent":false,"startDate":{"month":6,"year":1986},"title":"Graphic Designer"}]}</str><str name="user_locations">Southend on Sea, United Kingdom</str><str name="linkedin_skills">{"_total":5,"values":[{"id":1,"skill":{"name":"Adobe Creative Suite"}},{"id":2,"skill":{"name":"InDesign"}},{"id":3,"skill":{"name":"Graphics"}},{"id":13,"skill":{"name":"Exhibition Stands"}},{"id":14,"skill":{"name":"Plastic Printing"}}]}</str><str name="id">254</str><str name="name">Graphic Designer</str><str name="user_first_name">Tracy</str><str name="linkedin_summary"/><date name="last_modified">2013-09-20T09:17:00Z</date><arr name="content_type"><str>application/vnd.openxmlformats-officedocument.wordprocessingml.document</str></arr><arr name="content"><str>                 Name:	Tracy Georgina Munden  Address: 	289 London Road, Benfleet, Essex SS7 5XP  Telephone:	Mobile: 07572 547871  Email:	tgmdesign@hotmail.co.uk  Education: 	Jotmans Hall Primary School (1975-1981)  	Appleton Secondary School (1981-1986)  Further Education:	Gourley College (1986-1988)              	Qualifications:  	English Language	O-Level B	French		O-Level D  	English Literature	O-Level C	Physics	CSE 3  	Mathematics		O-Level C	Chemistry	CSE 3  	History			O-Level C	Art		CSE 3  	North Western Regional Advisory Council for Further Education (NWRAC):  	Graphic Technology Course  	Graphic Imagery (A)	Credit         Lettering and Design	              Pass  	Graphic Imagery (B)	Credit         Process Camera Techniques	  Pass  Systems Used:	Apple Macintosh, Crosfield Pat/Sunsparc and Studiobank/Studiostream,  	Scitex System, Ryobi and Konica Digital Press.  Applications Used:	QuarkXpress, Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign, Dreamweaver, Communigator,  	Pagemaker, ADS, Flightchecker, Preps, Scitex Gateway Tools, Scitex Colourfill.     Olympus KeyMed   KeyMed House, Stock Road, Southend-on-Sea, Essex.   Position:  Senior Graphic Designer       April 2000 - August 2013  I was employed here to design and produce final print ready artwork for our in-house print room. I produced a variety of artwork from simple stationery and course literature to full colour brochures and promotional leaflets, as well as slides for web sites and powerpoint presentations. I also produced designs for product launches, banner stands and give away items for exhibitions and in-house courses, for example; bags, polo-shirts, plaques, pens and DVD covers. Recently I had been producing more promotional literature, packaging and adverts for the Olympus camera ranges and also emailers for marketing purposes. The company supported many charities and schools, therefore I was expected to liaise directly with clients and to oversee all projects from start to finish, including approving all printed items and ensuring delivery to the clients.     Thames Card Technology   Thames House, Arterial Road, Rayleigh, Essex.   Position:  Studio Manager       April 1998 - April 2000  I was employed here to oversee the installation of the Scitex colour system within the Studio department. I managed all production of work and trained other members of staff to operate the system and to use the Iris Realist proofer and Dolev 4Press. I liaised directly with clients and with our Sales Representatives on a daily basis. The work I produced was mainly laminated cards, store cards and various forms of plastic printing.     Fairway Litho Print Services Limited   3/4 Seax Way, Southfields Industrial Park, Laindon, Essex.   Position:  Designer, Typesetter and Scitex System Operator       November 1995 - April 1998  I was employed here to produce final film, Iris Realist colour proofs and page layout for the Scitex system. I produced a variety of work but mainly magazines, posters and computer game packages. I also designed and typeset brochures, business stationery and adverts for magazines. A few of the magazines were produced with APR pictures, for which I was responsible. All files and pictures were sent and received using ISDN or Modem lines. I was expected to liaise with clients on their requirements and keep all digital information and relevant paperwork.     Cloverleaf Graphics   Charfleets Farm Industrial Park, Canvey Island, Essex.   Position:  Designer, Typesetter and Crosfield System Operator       June 1991 - November 1995  I was employed here to operate a Crosfield Colour System to produce four colour film. I typeset on an Apple Macintosh using a variety of programmes. I originally used a Crosfield Pat/Sunsparc System and then a Crosfield Studiostream and Studiobank System. I produced a variety of work but mainly brochures, magazines, compact disc, video and album sleeves. I was the only System operator and was expected to work without supervision to meet deadlines. I also trained three other members of staff to use the system and was expected to liaise directly with many of our clients.     Kall-Kwik Printing   32 Southchurch Road, Southend-on-Sea, Essex.   Position: Head of Art Department       March 1989 - June 1991  At this company I started to design and typeset on an Apple Macintosh, I was self taught using the supplied manuals. The work was varied, from general stationery to full colour brochures. I was expected to take briefs directly from clients and produce camera ready and colour separated artwork, for our in-house printing department. I used a Copy Lyn camera to produce logos and photographs and was expected to draw new logos either on the Apple Macintosh or by hand. I also taught two trainees how to use the Apple Macintosh and camera.     Redlin Print Limited   Manor Road Trading Estate, Benfleet, Essex.   Position: Graphic Designer       July 1987 - March 1989  I started as a trainee and progressed to a full-time employee. I was the only artist and designed and produced all artwork without supervision.   I used an Agfa 2001 camera and also made negatives and plates. I produced a variety of work from general stationery to full colour brochures.     College / Work Experience       June 1986 - July 1987  During this time I attended college and also worked as a trainee to learn Graphic Design, originally hand drawing artwork using Letraset and Rotoring pens. I worked within two companies, Pip Printers and Creative Services Limited. I was taught how to use camera’s to produce negatives and film for artwork and also how to layout and space text. Later I learnt how to split artwork to produce film and colour plates for printing.   </str></arr><long name="_version_">1449143311563489280</long></doc></result>
</response>